pakistaniyan.com 2015-12-24

# Privacy Policy | Pakistaniyan

**Privacy Policy**

The privacy of our visitors/users of “http://Pakistaniyan.com” is really important to us.

At http://Pakistaniyan.com, we know that privacy of your personal information (if provided on our website by you) is important. Here is the detailed information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit http://Pakistaniyan.com , and how we safeguard your information.  One thing is to be mentioned here that we never sell (and never will) your personal information to third parties at any cost.

**Log Files:**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.  The information in the log files include  your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons:**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.  This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on http://Pakistaniyan.com to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (like [Google](http://blazomania.com/category/google/ "Google") through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**DoubleClick DART cookies:**

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements).  This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (“interest based targeting”).  The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey).  DART uses “non personally identifiable information”.  It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.  You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx)

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.  This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program.  Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

**Email Addresses:**

If you enter your e-mail address where we demanded (On Comments etc), please be assured that your email address will only be used for responding to your email or comment and will never be made publicly available. We will never sell your email address to any third parties, ever.

**Comments Policy:**

The owner/writer/author does not assume responsibility over comments he did not make on this website. While comments can be posted by anyone from anywhere regardless of country, we reserve the right to remove any comment that is not deemed suitable for publication. This could include but is not limited to objectionable and abusive comments. Hate, racist comments, or any other form of prejudice will be removed and the poster will be banned!

Comments made for sole purpose of getting back-links or advertizing your/any product will not be accepted. Link to third party website will require moderation and we reserve the rights to edit/delete such links.

Spam in any form will not be accepted and will be deleted immediately. We may take action against such spammers and we may block spammer permanently from the website.

We have integrated Facebook Comments on our website as well so anyone is free to comments on the posts and Pakistaniyan's Team is not responsible for every comment posted by users on the website but we are watching the comments and moderating them on daily basis. 

**Copyrights:**

Supreme caution has been taken to make sure that there are no copyright infringements in terms of the multimedia content and the subject matter that is posted in this blog. If you find anything that could be considered a violation of the copyright norms, then **kindly report us** ( **Pakistaniyan at gmail dot com** ) **before any legal action**. We will remove that material with apology as soon as possible.

Thank You!

Pakistaniyan –It's all about Pakistan and Its People
